A Guide to the Harry F. Byrd Jr. Papers
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library, #10320-a, -b
Harry F. Byrd, Jr. Papers ca. 1954-1982
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
10320-a, -b
ca. 310,200 items
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access to the Harry F. Byrd, Jr., Papers is controlled by the Honorable Harry F. Byrd, Jr. An applicant for access who is not associated with the University of Virginia must furnish to the Director of Special Collections a brief description of his academic or other qualifications, a summary of his research project, and a description of any projected publication that might make use of material from, or material derived from, the Harry F. Byrd, Jr., Papers. The Director of Special Collections will contact Senator Byrd and will notify the applicant of the Senator's decision.
Acquisition Information
These two additions to the Harry F. Byrd, Jr. Papers were given to the Library by Harry F. Byrd, Jr. of Winchester, Virginia, on January 14, 1981 (10320-a) and December 16, 1982 (10320-b).
Scope and Content
These additions to the papers of Harry F. Byrd, Jr., of Winchester, Virginia, consist of ca. 310,200 items (588 Hollinger boxes and 50 cubics) ca. 1954-1982, chiefly papers pertaining to his years of service in the United States Senate. These include speeches, legislative files, transitional files from the beginning of his Senatorial career, administrative files, publicity files, public activity files, cassette tapes, printed material, memorabilia, index cards, certificates and awards, bound volumes, and photographs.
Decisions concerning the processing and retention of individual files were made by the Curator based upon the recommendations in Records Management Handbook for United States Senators and Their Repositories by Karen Dawley Paul, Archivist Senate Historical Office.
The first series contains both typed manuscript and electrostatic copies of speeches by Senator Byrd and statements released by his office; copies of the Congressional Record inserts included by Byrd; and press releases concerning speeches. This series is the only group of papers in this collection kept by Byrd's staff in regular chronological order. The remainder of Byrd's papers were filed in reverse chronological order by the staff and that order has been maintained for the rest of the collection.
The second and largest series in the collection consists of Senator Byrd's legislative files which are listed alphabetically in the box listing by folder heading and are arranged in reverse chronological order within each year. The filing arrangement used by Byrd's office changed in 1972 from previous years; the original folder heading was retained for individual files but the collection has been arranged in several series for the convenience of the researcher. A complete list of the folder headings can be found in the box listing but several topics of interest are noted in this paragraph. These include: agriculture (Boxes 13-24); American Revolution Bicentennial Commission(Boxes 25-27); armed services (Boxes 41-75); Byrd's committee work, the largest number of files being for the Armed Services Committee(Boxes 146-148) and the Finance Committee(Boxes 148-158); correspondence with other Senators and Congressmen (Boxes 161-177); the Byrd Amendment concerning Judge Tenure (Boxes 187-188); the Supreme Court (Boxes 191-193); Jimmy Carter's Policy on Energy (Box 226); the Energy Crisis (Boxes 227-239); the New York City Bailout (Boxes 177-179); the Arab-Israeli War and Middle East conflict (Boxes 263-265, 271-273); the Central America conflict (Boxes 266-268); Iran (Boxes 270-271); the Panama Canal Treaty (Boxes 274-283); Rhodesia and chrome (Boxes 283-285); relations with the Soviet Union (Boxes 285-287); Saudi Arabia (Boxes 287-288); Henry Kissinger (Boxes 288-289); the VietnamWar and public opinion (Boxes 291-295, & 329); the restoration of citizenship to Robert E. Lee (Boxes 328-329); the Taft-Hartley Act (Boxes 359-362); political affairs (Boxes 383-392); communications from the office of the President (Boxes 405-411); federal tax reform (Boxes 429-441); revenue- sharing (Boxes 454-456); Virginia affairs (Boxes 463-499); the Portsmouth Public School controversy (Box 496); and Watergate and public opinion (Boxes 499-510).
The third series constitutes the transitional files, ca. 1964-1966, in use by Byrd's office when he was appointed to complete his father's term in the Senate in 1965, including memoranda files concerning upcoming legislation (Boxes 528-529), speech drafts for 1966 (Box 530), and civil rights files, 1965-1966 (Box 528).
The administrative files comprises the fourth series of the collection and includes memoranda to and from the staff and the legislative and administrative assistants, White House nominations, form letters, and other office concerns.
The fifth series consists of the personal papers of Senator Byrd, including files concerning the controversy over the Jack Anderson column about Byrd; biographic material; Byrd business papers (1970-1972); Byrd family papers (1954-1982); caricatures of political figures by Jeff MacNelly (Box 548) including Harry F. Byrd, Jr., Richard M. Nixon, Mills Godwin, Gerald Ford, Henry Kissinger, Lyndon B. Johnson, and others; miscellaneous photographs of Byrd with various groups and individuals (Box 549); and Byrd's South Pole trip to commemorate the fiftieth anniversary of the flight of his uncle, Richard E. Byrd, over the South Pole in 1929 (Box 549).
The sixth series contains publicity files, chiefly newsletter responses from constituents, press correspondence and requests, and newsclippings concerning the Senator and his activities.
The public activities files in series seven has folders on the Annie J. Bronson Charitable Foundation; appointments; donations; 1976 election congratulations, campaign invitations and questionnaires (this is the only campaign related material in this collection, except for a few pieces of memorabilia); invitations accepted; memorablilia, including bicentennial flags, first day covers, medallions and commemorative coins, presidential ceremonial pens from Jimmy Carter and Ronald Reagan, campaign buttons, patches, pins, and a 1970 election rubber stamp "Virginians Vote for Byrd"; and VIP correspondence files, created by culling especially notable correspondents from transitory and temporary files not otherwise retained with the rest of the collection. Correspondents are noted in the folder listing for boxes 585-587.
Series eight consists of miscellaneous papers and materials including cassette tapes removed from the collection and stored separately, fifty cubics of daily carbons, 1973-1982, which this department hopes to microfilm at a later date, oversize material, and a card file tray containing 3 x 5 index cards with the filing categories used by Byrd's office after 1972.
Organization
The original folder arrangement of the Harry F. Byrd, Jr. papers was entirely alphabetical. Because the collection was a large one, several series were created by separating the files pertaining directly to legislation from the others. All of Byrd's papers, excluding the speech series, were in reverse chronological order and this order has been maintained within each year. The years have been arranged with the earliest year coming first in sequence.
Series I: Speeches (Boxes 1-12)
Series II: Legislative Files (Boxes 13-527)
Series III: Transitional Legislative Files (Boxes 528-530)
Series IV: Administration Files (Boxes 530-541)
Series V: Personal Papers (Boxes 542-549)
Series VI: Publicity (Boxes 550-560)
Series VII: Public Activities (Boxes 560-588)
Series VIII: Miscellaneous Papers
Subseries A: Cassette Tapes (T-931-937)
Subseries B: Daily Carbons (50 Cubics)
Subseries C: Oversize Folder
Subseries D: Card File Tray # 71
Container List
- Series I: Speeches
  - Speeches, 1973 January-September 17; (6 folders) (Box Box 1)
  - Speeches, 1973 September 18-1974 May 16; (5 folders) (Box Box 2)
  - Speeches, 1974 May 20-October; (6 folders) (Box Box 3)
  - Speeches, 1974 November-1975 March 11; (6 folders) (Box Box 4)
  - Speeches, 1975 March 12-July 16; (6 folders) (Box Box 5)
  - Speeches, 1975 July 21-November 11; (5 folders) (Box Box 6)
  - Speeches, 1975 November 12-1976 April 14; (6 folders) (Box Box 7)
  - Speeches, 1976 April 22-July; (5 folders) (Box Box 8)
  - Speeches, 1976 August-1977 January; (5 folders) (Box Box 9)
  - Speeches, 1977 February-1978 April 18; (7 folders) (Box Box 10)
  - Speeches, 1978 April 20-1979 June 13; (6 folders) (Box Box 11)
  - Speeches, 1979 June 18-1980 December 18; (6 folders) (Box Box 12)
- Series II: Legislative Files
  - Agriculture, 1973-1977 August-December; (6 folders) (Box Box 13)
  - Agriculture, 1977 January-July, -1979; (6 folders) (Box Box 14)
  - Agriculture, 1980-1982 June-November; (6 folders) (Box Box 15)
  - Agriculture, 1982 January-May (Box Box 16)
  - Agriculture: Agriculture & Consumer Protection Act of 1973 (S. 1888), (2 folders) (Box Box 16)
  - Agriculture: Apples, 1973-1978 (Box Box 16)
  - Agriculture: Appropriation Bill (H.R. 15690), 1971-1972 (Box Box 16)
  - Agriculture: Cattle, 1973-1978; (2 folders) (Box Box 16)
  - Agriculture: Cattle (Diethylstilbestrol), 1973 (Box Box 16)
  - Agriculture: Coffee, 1977 (Box Box 17)
  - Agriculture: Commodities, 1973-1977; (3 folders) (Box Box 17)
  - Agriculture: Conservation, 1972-1978; (2 folders) (Box Box 17)
  - Agriculture: Cotton, 1973-1975 (Box Box 17)
  - Agriculture: Dairy Products, 1973-1977; (2 folders) (Box Box 17)
  - Agriculture: Extension Service, 1973 (Box Box 18)
  - Agriculture: Farmers Home Administration, 1973-1978; (4 folders) (Box Box 18)
  - Agriculture: Fertilizer, 1975 (Box Box 18)
  - Agriculture: Fish, 1973 (Box Box 18)
  - Agriculture: Food, 1977-1981; (3 folders) (Box Box 18)
  - Agriculture: Food Stamps, 1973-1975 March-July; (7 folders) (Box Box 19)
  - Agriculture: Food Stamps, 1975 January-February-1980; (7 folders) (Box Box 20)
  - Agriculture: Food Stamps, 1981 (Box Box 21)
  - Agriculture: Honeybees, 1974-1978 (Box Box 21)
  - Agriculture: Horses, 1973-1976 (Box Box 21)
  - Agriculture: Marketing and Bargaining, 1973 (Box Box 21)
  - Agriculture: Meat Inspection, 1973-1980; (2 folders) (Box Box 21)
  - Agriculture: Peanuts, 1973-1980; (2 folders) (Box Box 21)
  - Agriculture: Poultry, 1973-1980 (Box Box 21)
  - Agriculture: Rice, 1976 (Box Box 21)
  - Agriculture: Rural Development, 1973-1974 (Box Box 21)
  - Agriculture: Rural Environmental Assistance Program, 1973 February-September (Box Box 21)
  - Agriculture: Rural Environmental Assistance Program, 1973; (3 folders) (Box Box 22)
  - Agriculture: School Lunch Program, 1972, 1976-1981 (Box Box 22)
  - Agriculture: Soil Bank, 1973-1977 (Box Box 22)
  - Agriculture: Soil Surveys, 1974-1982 (Box Box 22)
  - Agriculture: Soybeans, 1973-1975 (Box Box 22)
  - Agriculture: Sugar, 1974-1977 (Box Box 22)
  - Agriculture: Tobacco, 1973-1982; (7 folders) (Box Box 23)
  - Agriculture: Tobacco (Flue Cured and Burley), 1973-1977 (Box Box 23)
  - Agriculture: Tobacco (Health Hazard Claims), 1973-1978 (Box Box 23)
  - Agriculture: Wheat, 1973-1979; (2 folders) (Box Box 24)
  - Agriculture: World Hunger, 1976-1982; (5 folders) (Box Box 24)
  - American Revolution Bicentennial Commission, 1972-1979; (7 folders) (Box Box 25)
  - American Revolution Bicentennial Commission: Cultural Laureate Foundation, 1972-1980; (4 folders) (Box Box 26)
  - American Revolution Bicentennial Commission: Virginia Projects, 1973-1974 May-December; (3 folders) (Box Box 26)
  - American Revolution Bicentennial Commission: Virginia Projects, 1974 January-April-1980; (8 folders) (Box Box 27)
  - Appropriations, 1975-1980 June-December; (8 folders) (Box Box 28)
  - Appropriations, 1980 January-May, 1981 October-December; (8 folders) (Box Box 29)
  - Appropriations, 1981 June-September; (7 folders) (Box Box 30)
  - Appropriations, 1981 April-May; (9 folders) (Box Box 31)
  - Appropriations, 1981 February 19-March; (7 folders) (Box Box 32)
  - Appropriations, 1981 January-February-1982 April-December; (6 folders) (Box Box 33)
  - Appropriations, 1982 January-March; (4 folders) (Box Box 34)
  - Appropriations: Agriculture, 1973-1981 (Box Box 34)
  - Appropriations: Continuing, 1973-1982 (Box Box 34)
  - Appropriations: Defense, 1973-1976 (Box Box 34)
  - Appropriations: Expenditure Control, 1973-1981 (Box Box 34)
  - Appropriations: Foreign Assistance, 1973-1974; (2 folders) (Box Box 34)
  - Appropriations: Foreign Assistance, 1975-1976; (3 folders) (Box Box 35)
  - Appropriations: Housing and Urban Development, 1973-1975 (Box Box 35)
  - Appropriations: Impoundment of Funds, 1973; (5 folders) (Box Box 35)
  - Appropriations: Impoundment of Funds (Petitions), 1973 (Box Box 36)
  - Appropriations: Interior, 1973-1978 (Box Box 36)
  - Appropriations: Labor and Health, Education & Welfare, 1973-1976; (4 folders) (Box Box 36)
  - Appropriations: Labor and Health, Education & Welfare, 1977-1979; (7 folders) (Box Box 37)
  - Appropriations: Labor and Health, Education & Welfare, 1980-1981 May-December; (8 folders) (Box Box 38)
  - Appropriations: Labor and Health, Education & Welfare, 1981 January-April; (6 folders) (Box Box 39)
  - Appropriations: Labor and Health, Education & Welfare (H.R. 16654), 1972 (Box Box 39)
  - Appropriations: Labor and Health, Education & Welfare (Education), 1982; (5 folders) (Box Box 40)
  - Appropriations: Public Works, 1973-1978 (Box Box 40)
  - Appropriations: State, Justice, Commerce, 1973-1975, 1980-1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 40)
  - Appropriations: Supplemental, 1974 (Box Box 40)
  - Appropriations: Transportation, 1974-1979 (Box Box 40)
  - Appropriations: Treasury & Post Office, 1973-1982 (Box Box 41)
  - Armed Services, 1973-1976; (5 folders) (Box Box 41)
  - Armed Services, 1977 April-December; (8 folders) (Box Box 42)
  - Armed Services, 1977 January-March, 1978 June-December; (7 folders) (Box Box 43)
  - Armed Services, 1978 January-May; (6 folders) (Box Box 44)
  - Armed Services, 1979-1980 August-December; (8 folders) (Box Box 45)
  - Armed Services, 1980 January-July, 1981 October-December; (8 folders) (Box Box 46)
  - Armed Services, 1981 January-September, 1982; (7 folders) (Box Box 47)
  - Armed Services: Academies, 1974-1981 (Box Box 47)
  - Armed Services: Appropriations, 1973-1981; (7 folders) (Box Box 48)
  - Armed Services: Appropriations, 1982 (Box Box 49)
  - Armed Services: B-1 Bomber, 1974-1982; (5 folders) (Box Box 49)
  - Armed Services: Base Closings, 1979 (Box Box 50)
  - Armed Services: CHAMPUS, 1973-1982; (7 folders) (Box Box 50)
  - Armed Services: CHAMPUS (Ft. Lee), 1977; (2 folders) (Box Box 51)
  - Armed Services: Defense, 1979 & 1981 (Box Box 51)
  - Armed Services: Defense Appropriation Bill, 1973-1977 August-December; (4 folders) (Box Box 51)
  - Armed Services: Defense Appropriation Bill, 1977 January-July,1978-1979; (7 folders) (Box Box 52)
  - Armed Services: Defense Appropriation Bill, 1980-1982; (4 folders) (Box Box 53)
  - Armed Services: Defense Appropriation Bill, 1978-1982; (8 folders) (Box Box 53)
  - Armed Services: Defense Contractors, 1973-1975, 1981-1982; (4 folders) (Box Box 53)
  - Armed Services: Defense Contracts - TYCO, 1971-1973 (Box Box 54)
  - Armed Services: Disability Retirement, 1972-1979; (2 folders) (Box Box 54)
  - Armed Services: Facilities, 1973-1974, 1975 November-December; (4 folders) (Box Box 54)
  - Armed Services: Facilities, 1975 March-October; (7 folders) (Box Box 55)
  - Armed Services: Facilities, 1975 January-February, 1976-1977; (6 folders) (Box Box 56)
  - Armed Services: Facilities, 1978-1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 57)
  - Armed Services: Facilities (Ft. Eustis), 1974-1979 (Box Box 57)
  - Armed Services: Facilities (Ft. Monroe), 1973-1981; (3 folders) (Box Box 57)
  - Armed Services: Facilities (Ft. Story), 1973-1979 (Box Box 58)
  - Armed Services: Facilities (Navy), 1973-1978; (6 folders) (Box Box 58)
  - Armed Services: Facilities (Navy), 1979-1982; (5 folders) (Box Box 59)
  - Armed Services: Facilities (Radford), 1976 (Box Box 59)
  - Armed Services: Facilities (U.S.S. Yorktown), 1973-1974 (Box Box 59)
  - Armed Services: Federal Contract Research Centers, 1979 (Box Box 59)
  - Armed Services: Foreign Military Export Sales (S 2662), 1976 (Box Box 59)
  - Armed Services: Manpower, 1972-1982; (7 folders) (Box Box 60)
  - Armed Services: Manpower Assignments, 1973-1978 (Box Box 61)
  - Armed Services: National Guard and the Volunteer Army, 1973-1982; (4 folders) (Box Box 61)
  - Armed Services: Pay, 1973 (Box Box 61)
  - Armed Services: Pay, 1974-1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 62)
  - Armed Services: Preparedness, 1973-1977; (2 folders) (Box Box 62)
  - Armed Services: Procurement, 1974-1981 (Box Box 62)
  - Armed Services: Promotion of Officers, 1972-1976, 1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 62)
  - Armed Services: Reserves (Naval), 1973-1982; (8 folders) (Box Box 63)
  - Armed Services: Retirement, 1973-1977 March-December; (7 folders) (Box Box 64)
  - Armed Services: Retirement, 1977 January-February, 1978-1979; (8 folders) (Box Box 65)
  - Armed Services: Retirement, 1980-1982; (7 folders) (Box Box 66)
  - Armed Services: Salt Talks, 1973-1978 (Box Box 66)
  - Armed Services: Salt Talks, 1979 August-December; (7 folders) (Box Box 67)
  - Armed Services: Salt Talks, 1979 January-July, 1980; (6 folders) (Box Box 68)
  - Armed Services: Selective Service, 1973-1974; (7 folders) (Box Box 69)
  - Armed Services: Selective Service, 1975-1979; (7 folders) (Box Box 70)
  - Armed Services: Selective Service, 1980-1982; (7 folders) (Box Box 71)
  - Armed Services: Ship Sales & Loans, 1973-1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 72)
  - Armed Services: Strategic Materials, 1973-1974 April-December; (6 folders) (Box Box 72)
  - Armed Services: Strategic Materials, 1974 January-March, 1975-1982; (4 folders) (Box Box 73)
  - Armed Services: Unions, 1976-1977; (5 folders) (Box Box 73)
  - Armed Services: Weapons, 1973-1981, 1982 May-December; (7 folders) (Box Box 74)
  - Armed Services: Weapons, 1982 January-April; (3 folders) (Box Box 75)
  - Banking & Currency, 1973-1976; (4 folders) (Box Box 75)
  - Banking & Currency, 1977-1982; (5 folders) (Box Box 76)
  - Banking & Currency: Bad Debts, 1977 (Box Box 76)
  - Banking & Currency: Banking Reform, 1973-1978; (3 folders) (Box Box 77)
  - Banking & Currency: Bonds - Public & Savings, 1973-1981 (Box Box 77)
  - Banking & Currency: Consumer Co-op Bank Bill, 1978 (Box Box 77)
  - Banking & Currency: Credit, 1973-1978 (Box Box 77)
  - Banking & Currency: Devaluation of the Dollar, 1973-1974 (Box Box 77)
  - Banking & Currency: Export-Import Bank, 1974-1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 78)
  - Banking & Currency: Federal Credit Unions, 1973-1980 (Box Box 78)
  - Banking & Currency: Federal Financing Bank, 1972-1974 (Box Box 78)
  - Banking & Currency: Federal Reserve System, 1973-1981; (3 folders) (Box Box 78)
  - Banking & Currency: Gold, 1973-1979; (2 folders) (Box Box 78)
  - Banking & Currency: Interest Rates, 1973-1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 79)
  - Banking & Currency: Mortgage, 1974-1976 (Box Box 79)
  - Banking & Currency: One Bank Holding Company, 1973 (Box Box 79)
  - Banking & Currency: Savings & Loan, 1973-1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 79)
  - Banking & Currency: Securities and Exchange Commission, 1973-1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 79)
  - Banking & Currency: Unclaimed Property, 1973 (Box Box 79)
  - Budget, 1975-1980; (7 folders) (Box Box 80)
  - Budget, 1981-1982; (4 folders) (Box Box 81)
  - Budget: Expediture Controls, 1973 May-December; (2 folders) (Box Box 81)
  - Budget: Expediture Controls, 1973 January-April, 1974 April-December; (6 folders) (Box Box 82)
  - Budget: Expediture Controls, 1974 January-March, 1975-1980; (6 folders) (Box Box 83)
  - Budget: Management and Budget, 1973--1978; (2 folders) (Box Box 84)
  - Budget: Presidential Submissions, 1973-1982; (5 folders) (Box Box 84)
  - Civil Disorders, 1973-1976 (Box Box 84)
  - Civil Rights, 1972-1977; (6 folders) (Box Box 85)
  - Civil Rights, 1978-1982; (5 folders) (Box Box 86)
  - Civil Rights: Busing, 1971, 1973 May-December (Box Box 86)
  - Civil Rights: Busing, 1973 January-April, 1974-1976; (7 folders) (Box Box 87)
  - Civil Rights: Busing, 1977-1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 88)
  - Civil Rights: Central Intelligence Agency, 1975-1982; (6 folders) (Box Box 88)
  - Civil Rights: Commission on Civil Rights, 1974-1978 (Box Box 89)
  - Civil Rights: Constitutional Rights, 1973-1981 (Box Box 89)
  - Civil Rights: Discrimination, 1974-1982 (Box Box 89)
  - Civil Rights: English Language, 1982 (Box Box 89)
  - Civil Rights: Equal Rights, 1976-1982; (4 folders) (Box Box 89)
  - Civil Rights: Freedom of Information, Press, Speech, 1973-1982 (Box Box 89)
  - Civil Rights: Integration, 1973-1979 (Box Box 90)
  - Civil Rights: Prayer, 1973-1976; (5 folders) (Box Box 90)
  - Civil Rights: Prayer, 1977-1982; (6 folders) (Box Box 91)
  - Civil Rights: Privacy, 1974-1982 (Box Box 92)
  - Civil Rights: Quotas, 1975-1978; (4 folders) (Box Box 92)
  - Civil Rights: Religion, 1974-1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 92)
  - Civil Rights: Voting Rights, 1973-1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 93)
  - Civil Rights: Women's Rights, 1973-1976; (3 folders) (Box Box 93)
  - Civil Rights: Women's Rights, 1977-1978 March-December; (8 folders) (Box Box 94)
  - Civil Rights: Women's Rights, 1978 January-February, 1979-1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 95)
  - Civil Service, 1973-1982 (Box Box 95)
  - Civil Service: Air Traffic Controllers, 1977 & 1981 (Box Box 95)
  - Civil Service: Employment, 1974-1982; (3 folders) (Box Box 95)
  - Civil Service: Fringe Benefits, 1973-1981; (2 folders) (Box Box 96)
  - Civil Service: Hatch Act, 1975-1977 July-December; (5 folders) (Box Box 96)
  - Civil Service: Hatch Act, 1977 January-June, 1978-1979; (2 folders) (Box Box 97)
  - Civil Service: Health Benefits, 1973-1982; (4 folders) (Box Box 97)
  - Civil Service: Operations, 1981 (Box Box 97)
  - Civil Service: Pay Raises, 1973 (Box Box 97)
  - Civil Service: Pay Raises, 1974-1975 September 5-December; (8 folders) (Box Box 98)
  - Civil Service: Pay Raises, 1975 January-September 4, 1976-1982; (6 folders) (Box Box 99)
  - Civil Service: Reduction-in-Force, 1973, 1981 (Box Box 99)
  - Civil Service: Retirement, 1973 October-December (Box Box 99)
  - Civil Service: Retirement, 1971, 1973 January-June, 1974-75; (9 folders) (Box Box 100)
  - Civil Service: Retirement, 1976-1978 April-November; (8 folders) (Box Box 101)
  - Civil Service: Retirement, 1978 January-March, 1979-1980 August-December; (6 folders) (Box Box 102)
  - Civil Service: Retirement, 1980 January-July, 1981 April-December; (8 folders) (Box Box 103)
  - Civil Service: Retirement, 1981 January-March, 1982; (4 folders) (Box Box 104)
  - Civil Service: Strikes, 1981-1982 (Box Box 104)
  - Commerce, 1973-1979; (3 folders) (Box Box 104)
  - Commerce, 1980-1982; (5 folders) (Box Box 105)
  - Commerce: Airline Deregulation, 1977 June-December; (2 folders) (Box Box 105)
  - Commerce: Airline Deregulation, 1977 January-May; (2 folders) (Box Box 106)
  - Commerce: Airports, 1973-1980; (5 folders) (Box Box 106)
  - Commerce: Airports - Dulles, 1973-1975 (Box Box 106)
  - Commerce: Airports - Dulles, 1976-1980; (2 folders) (Box Box 107)
  - Commerce: Airports - Ft. Belvoir, 1973 (Box Box 107)
  - Commerce: Animals (Transportation of), 1973-1976 (Box Box 107)
  - Commerce: Aviation, 1972-1973, 1974 June-December; (3 folders) (Box Box 107)
  - Commerce: Aviation, 1974 January-May, 1975; (7 folders) (Box Box 108)
  - Commerce: Aviation, 1976-1977; (6 folders) (Box Box 109)
  - Commerce: Aviation, 1978-1980; (6 folders) (Box Box 110)
  - Commerce: Aviation, 1981-1982; (5 folders) (Box Box 111)
  - Commerce: Balance of Trade, 1973 (Box Box 111)